Yes, it's taken long enough, but I finally found a group of people with such nice memories.
Oh, my God.
Oh, you're awake.
You feel okay?
Who are you?
Huh?
Was it lost?
Stolen?
Who are you?
Who said I don't want any more food?
Oh, my God.
Keep it coming.
Look, I somehow wake up in a different place
surrounded by people I've never seen before.
You got any answers?
Like maybe why I'm here?
Uh, no.
Hey, wait.
Are you telling me you aren't the guys
that drag me out of the drink?
Do what?
I'm Luffy.
I left my home in Fushia Village to go sailing yesterday,
but got caught in a giant whirlpool.
I remember climbing into a barrel and getting dizzy enough to puke,
and then I woke up in this place.
So I thought you guys saved me or something.
What? None of this adds up.
All I did yesterday was shoot the breeze with Gaia
and then played some games with Pepper and the other kids.
None of that explains how I woke up here.
And it's the same for them.
So, you have any idea what's going on?
Huh?
Neither of us have a clue and that only leaves you.
Oh, they might find me useless and kill me
if I don't give them an answer.
I'll just have to try and bluff my way through this.
All right, if you really want to know,
you probably don't remember anything
because your mind's trying to repress your terror.
I mean, you were attacked by a legendary giant whale, after all.
We were attacked by a giant whale?
You got it.
It swallowed you guys whole,
but I managed to easily defeat it
and pull you two out of its belly.
Wow, you did all that?
Thank you.
Does our brave savior have a name?
That's the million berry question!
I am the fearless and much feared leader
of the notorious pirate crew that rules over the East Blue!
The people fear me and love me in equal measure!
I am known as the intrepid Captain Usopp!
Wow!
You mean the Captain Usopp?
What, you know him?
Never heard of him!
Careful!
You want to make sure you stay on my good side!
I do preside over an army of 8,000 pirates, after all!
You what?!
8,000 men?!
Oh, and, uh, you both joined up as my servants yesterday!
We did!
You're lying.
Ah!
How'd you know?
Well, I know you are now.
Ah!
You tricked me into giving myself away!
You're a funny guy, Captain!
You mocking me?
No one mocks me!
I've got too much pride for mockery, dammit!
In fact, I've got so much pride,
everyone I know calls me Usopp the Proud!
What's up?
Something wrong?
Yeah.
Oh, it's just...
I feel like I've done this before.
Same here.
You're an idiot.
But that's the least of my concerns now.
What we need is food.
I mean, how can you expect us to remember anything on an empty stomach?
Yeah, didn't you say you were some kind of cook?
A first-class cook.
They've got to have food somewhere aboard this ship.
First class?
Hey, hold on a second.
So tell me, what exactly is your story, anyway?
My story?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates someday!
Oh, man.
This ship has definitely seen better days.
Land!
Check it out!
I wonder what island that is!
We have a bit of a problem, you guys.
It's our navigator here.
Oh, who are those two?
Are they part of your giant pirate crew, Captain?
Hmm?
Uh, yeah!
That's it!
Don't tell me you've lost your memories, too.
I now understand how foolish a moth must feel as it's helplessly drawn toward the flame.
I'm irresistibly compelled to leap headfirst into the brilliant radiance of the beauty before me.
Enchante, gorgeous ladies.
I'm Sanji.
I would love to treat you to a gourmet dinner tonight if you're available.
Hmm.
He's almost as funny as you are!
He's like a different person all of a sudden.
Ah!
All right!
Who are these creeps and where am I?
Also...
Isn't that backwards?
Ah!
Uh...
What's that thing?
A deer.
Shut your pie, ho, human!
I'm a reindeer!
It just talked!
Ah!
Hey!
I say we catch it!
Ah!
Stop!
Leave that thing alone!
Ah!
Great girl!
Help me grab this!
What?
No way!
Fuzz off, loser!
Oh boy!
Where do I even begin to explain this to them?
Put it over here!
Wait down!
Ow!
We're chasing them, you little damn monsters!
Ah!
It's currently located somewhere in the Grand Line.
Did any of you remember that?
The Grand Line?
Oh ha ha!
Are you seriously happy about this?
The Grand Line is supposed to be teeming with all sorts
of creepy monsters and dangerous stuff!
As I see it, the only rational reaction here is to
panic and freak out!
Really?
It just looks like the regular OT.
Are you sure this is the Grand Line?
Navigator?
Uh, why are you looking at me?
Do you recognize the device you've got
strapped on your arm?
Hmm? What's that?
It's called a log pose.
Huh?
Your standard compass doesn't work here,
so we have to use the island's magnetic fields.
And that is the tool we use to follow them.
It's the only way that it's even possible to navigate the Grand Line.
Excuse me, Miss, do you have any suggestions
on how I can get back to my restaurant in the East Blue?
The last thing I need is to lose my job.
You don't want to do that.
Trust me, it's taken us a ridiculously long time
to reach this point in our journey.
Heading back on your own would be suicide.
Just take a look.
We've been following the log pose coordinates for quite some time,
and they've led us directly to this coral reef-surrounded island.
You don't actually expect me to believe any of this, do you?
Why would I possibly travel with a group of people
I have nothing in common with?
That's why.
Hey, wait, isn't that a pirate flag?
You mean we're on a pirate ship?
I already told you,
you're on the intrepid Captain Usopp's pirate ship.
For real?
You know what's kind of odd, Captain Usopp?
The fact that your Jolly Roger is wearing a straw hat.
Huh?
It is?
Uh, that's because this hat is mine.
Hey, no it's not!
Give it back!
You can touch my hat one more time
and I'll kick your butt to the other side of the ocean!
What's the deal?
How can you remember that it's your hat?
I remember all right.
This hat is like treasure to me.
Treasure?
A friend gave it to me when I was little,
and it means a whole lot.
I swore on this hat that one day I'd become a pirate
and gather up my own crew.
Pirate this, pirate that, who cares?
Although, one thing is certain now.
Everything you've told us is a big steaming pile of nonsense.
I hate pirates!
Every stinking last one of them!
So why would I be on this ship?
The only things I love are money and tangerines,
and I don't see either around here.
Hey now, I don't really see any reason
for you to be so rude to us.
Tangerines?
Like those?
Why are those on a ship?
What just happened?
Ah!
That tree grew an arm!
A mystery tree!
Just who the hell are you?
Aren't you a bit more curious about that?
I can tell it's one of Bellomere's tangerines.
I'd know them anywhere.
But what exactly are they doing here aboard this ship?
As much as I'd like to answer that question for you,
I'm actually uncertain of all the details.
If you really want to know,
then I suggest you check the logbook in your room.
Huh?
And if I remember correctly,
there's even a picture of your Bellomere inside of it.
It's my handwriting.
Bellomere!
Here!
Look how many I got!
A bunch of them are still green!
Come on, Nami!
Pay attention!
What?
They still tasted sweet!
You're not supposed to eat them!
They're merchandise!
It's okay, girls.
We can have a few of them for ourselves.
Yeah!
You're a real meanie, Nojiko!
I'm what?
All right, go on.
Get back to work.
I have to go back.
Something bad might have happened to Kokoyashi Village.
So then, what exactly is it?
It's a talking reindeer!
I have to go!
Here's how to do it!
Reindeer, and I have to go have some new things up.
Reindeer!
Reindeer, huh?
Creepy little hands!
That's a true delicacy right there,
especially when it's thinly sliced and slowly simmered with vegetables.
What? You mean we can eat it?
Greindeers' steak with berry sauce is even better, if you ask me.
Then steak it is!
That's enough!
I eat no human food, you sicko!
You really shouldn't eat him. I mean, he is the ship's doctor, after all.
It is?
Yes. He is a truly brilliant doctor. Better than any human you'll meet.
Isn't that right?
Shut up! You can praise me all you want, you stupid human, but don't think I like it or anything!
Really? You look like you do.
His name's Chopper. He's a reindeer, but he ate the human human fruit and gained human abilities.
He's not the only one. I ate the flower flower fruit and gained devil fruit powers.
And Luffy ate a devil fruit as well, didn't you?
Yup! I ate a gum gum fruit. My body's made of rubber.
Three people with devil fruit powers? This is terrifying!
And you guys are all pirates? Real pirates?
We are. Although, you're a pirate too, you know.
Well, I guess I'll allow it. You're officially a member of my crew!
What? But why?
You believe that guy?
In any case, we've been sailing these seas together for quite some time now as a seven-member crew.
Wait, seven?
You up there, swordsman? You want to come down?
Huh?
It's a little early for this much of a racket. I was trying to sleep.
What the heck? Who's this guy? State your name now!
You're not supposed to ask someone for their name unless you give them yours first, you know.
Oh, hi! I'm Luffy! So what's your name?
Huh? I'm Roro no Azoro.
The pirate hunter?
That's not a description I've ever applied to myself. Other people stuck me with it.
But you are still a bounty hunter, aren't you?
Yeah, but only when I'm starving or need money to live. It's not my profession or anything.
All right. But I'm guessing the only reason you're even here is because you're on the hunt for pirates.
Beats me. I haven't the slightest idea why I'm on this ship.
So, you guys notorious pirates or something?
This guy wants to sell our heads for money!
Well, fine then, bring it on! I've got 8,000 pirates under my command!
Really? Then I would imagine you have a pretty hefty bounty on your head.
And just as I was starting to get low on food money,
I'd be happy to take you on if that's what you want.
No, no, no! I don't want that! That's not what I meant at all!
Let's just take it easy, okay?
Is somebody gonna help me out over here?
Usopp doesn't have a bounty on him. Not even one single solitary bear.
I don't!
There's gotta be some way off this ship.
It's all gold! There's more than enough here to buy back Kokoyashi Village!
Now, how do I get it out of here?
Huh?
Well, that looks promising.
Ahh!
Woah!
What is that then?
Ahh!
Awesome! I can't believe this thing runs on land and water!
Huh, why'd she take off? That thing is neat!
But our date!
Hmph, I don't know what's going on here, but I don't see any point in sticking around.
What? Did he just jump overboard? Why is everybody leaving?
What the heck is wrong with these people?
That is what we're going to have to figure out. And quickly.
Bye.
See you next time.
Back on the next One Piece,
a mysterious boy with a horn and Robin's deduction.
You're never going to be king of the pirate.